A master director shining his light on the best rock band on the planet.
Shine a Light is a documentary, music film directed by Martin Scorsese.
Martin Scorsese’s electrifying concert documentary captures The Rolling Stones
live at New York’s Beacon Theatre during their A Bigger Bang tour.
Filmed over two nights in 2006 with an all-star team of cinematographers, the film combines dynamic performances with archival
footage and rare glimpses behind the scenes, offering a vibrant portrait of the band’s enduring energy and legacy.
Self - The Rolling Stones Vocals, Guitar, Harmonica, played by Mick Jagger.
Self - The Rolling Stones Guitar, Vocals, played by Keith Richards.
Self - The Rolling Stones Drums, played by Charlie Watts.
Self - The Rolling Stones Guitar, played by Ronnie Wood.
Self - The Rolling Stones Saxophone, Keyboards, played by Tim Ries.
Self - The Rolling Stones Vocals, played by Blondie Chaplin.
Shine a Light is a 2008 concert film directed by Martin Scorsese documenting the Rolling
Stones' 2006 Beacon Theatre performances during their A Bigger Bang Tour.
The film also includes archive footage from the band's career and makes use of digital
cinematography  for backstage sequences, the first time Scorsese used the technology in a film.
The film takes its title from the song of the same name,
featured on the band's 1972 album Exile on Main St.
A soundtrack album was released in April 2008 on the Universal label.
This is also the last movie by Paramount Classics, as the company merged into its
sister company Paramount Vantage after the movie was released.
The film explores themes of new york city, concert,
rock 'n' roll, legend, movie business.